Once again, the maidens gather
in the gardens of Acala
and cross the Tama River with smiles
as pure as those of the Shinsengumi.
Their bodies and hearts, never once
sullied, are clad in pure white clothes.
The pleats of their skirts
without a single wrinkle,
their blue sailor scarves
bothered not by the wind.
They walk slowly and delicately.
Metropolitan Hinominami High School,
the garden of the maidens.
(It's a coed school, though.)
Good morning to you, lovely viewers!
Girl Meets Deer
It's still so cold.
It rained yesterday, too.
Be careful, it's slippery. Are you okay?
Th-Thank you very much!
You're welcome.
Koshi Torako, a second-year student
at Metropolitan Hinominami High,
president of the student council
as well as Class 2-B's student rep.
She's attractive, smart,
and good at sports.
She's revered as the perfect girl at both school and around town.
She's wonderful!
Just as I planned.
But Koshi Torako, whose high school life
seems to be going so well,
has a secret she can't
tell anyone. And it's that...
She's a former delinquent!
I'm the one they call
the Wild Beast of Tokyo's Hino City!
My dark past of being a delinquent,
influenced by shonen manga.
If I get caught,
all the effort I put into my high
school debut being an honor student
will go down the drain!
Not that anyone could ever see
through my perfect disguise, though.
That's what she thought.
Until today, anyway.
Are you kidding me?
A suicide by hanging in episode one?!
I'm glad we're a late-night anime!
Not that it makes this any better!
Should I call the police? A doctor?
Detective Conan? No... Hajime-chan!
She's alive?
What? If it's not suicide,
why is she hanging from a place like that?
She has antlers?
Must be those things they sell at that
Mouse-land place in Tokyo... I mean Chiba!
But those would come right off, right?
Which means those are real antlers?
Deer antlers, by the looks of it.
Is she supposed to be a deer?!
Even if she is, aren't male deer
the only ones that grow antlers?
Male
Female
UMA Deer Woman
Is she some kind of new UMA?
The Mysterious Deer Woman
Or a monster from an evil organization?
Either way, that's an
incredible amount of snot.
Current temperature is 12°C.
Gross!
And now, animals have started to gather,
thinking she's carrion!
You want a piece of me?
You wanna piece of me, huh? Come at me!
Why is she trying to pick a fight
in this situation?
Should I help her?
She's staring hard at me!
The intensity of her gaze!
If I get caught up in this, I'll be late!
Honor students cannot be late!
I'll have to pretend I didn't see her
and hurry to school.
You're going to leave me here?
After seeing me like this,
you're still leaving me here?
M-Me? Of course not!
Not to mention, you just
somehow ended up there, right?
I'm running late.
I don't really have time to play.
Tomorrow, the news will say,
"A high schooler from Hino
got caught in power lines and died."
From now on, you'll remember my face
when you go down
this street every morning.
You'll regret this every day, thinking,
"I should've helped her that day."
Okay! Fine!
I'm alive!
This girl is freakin' heavy!
You bastard—
Miss, what were you doing up there?
I woke up this morning and there I was.
I wonder why.
Seriously, tell me why!
Thank you so much for helping me,
Miss Delinquent.
Don't mention it.
"Miss Delinquent"?
Huh?! Who do you think you're talking to?!
You, Miss!
Wh-What are you talking about?
Me? With this beautiful
and composed womanly appearance?
A delinquent? Th-That's not possible!
Really?
But you smell like one.
Smell like what?
My antlers are reacting, too.
What kind of sensor is that?
I have to get away from this girl.
I-It must be your imagination.
You may be mistaking me for someone else.
I'd better get going.
Try not to get stuck again, okay?
That was close.
I thought my disguise was perfect.
How did she...?
Who the hell was that girl?
Be seated, everyone.
I'd like to introduce
a transfer student today.
A transfer student?
I have a bad feeling about this.
Come on in.
Coming!
I knew it!
Huh?
Wh-Why are you stuck again already?
Learn from your mistakes!
You're kidding, right?!
Please introduce yourself, Shikanoko-san.
Notsu! I'm Shikanoko Noko. Call me Nokotan!
Nokotan!
What a funny girl.
What a deer.
Why is everyone welcoming her like that?
Am I the weird one here?
As for your seat...
The desk next to Koshi-san is open!
A common trope in school anime,
the conveniently-empty seat.
This is bad. If she says something weird
my high school life will be over!
I have to make the first move.
Good morning!
Hey, I saw you this morning.
So you're a transfer student?
I'm Koshi Torako. If you have
any questions, feel free to ask.
Thanks!
Wait, maybe this will be okay after all.
I guess I didn't need to worry so much.
You can call me whatever you like.
Whatever I like?
I was just overthinking things.
Okay!
Miss Delinquent!
Miss Delinquent...
Huh?
Let's be friends, Miss Delinquent!
Koshi-san is a delinquent?
Koshi-san, of all people?!
There must be a mistake!
Hello?! A deer just joined our class
and you're choosing to focus on this?!
W-Wait, a delinquent?
What are you talking about?
Please don't make false allegations.
My primal instincts are telling me
you're a delinquent.
Are you a wild animal?!
Also, you're a virgin.
My antlers are reacting, too.
What kind of system is that anyway?!
Koshi-san's a virgin?
I knew it!
Really?
Stay out of this, you extras!
Wh-What proof do you have
that I'm a virgin?
What? So you're not a virgin?
Well... that's...
Virginity confirmed.
VIRGIN
NARA PARK
TODAI-JI
KOFUKU-JI
It's Koshi-san!
She looks beautiful as always!
My disgraceful past was
just about to come to light,
but it looks like I'm safe for now.
Though I can't let my guard down!
I have to make sure that deer
won't expose me as a former delinquent!
To accomplish that,
I must make my move
before she opens her mouth again.
Who put this mountain of snacks here?
Wait a minute... The way they're wrapped...
These are deer crackers!
"Deer crackers."
The soul food of Nara Prefecture.
(Opinions may vary.)
Students on their graduation trips
often eat them for laughs,
but much like their taste, the joke
is a bit bland, and usually falls flat.
Who would do this?
It was her for sure!
Is that drool? What is she, a Merlion?
Excuse me, Shikanoko-san. What is this?
I'm returning the favor.
That's not what your face says.
You... whoopsies.
You saved me this morning, right?
That's to say thanks.
That was no big deal.
I don't need repayment.
What? Not satisfied with deer crackers?
That's not the problem.
Besides, why are you
suddenly being condescending?
How about I give you an antler then?
They come off?
Here.
I don't want that!
You can even eat them.
D-Does it have a taste?
Not that I'm going to try it...
No taste, no smell, super hard.
But you eat it anyway?!
If that's not enough... This is just for you.
I said I don't want it!
Maybe I'm not in the position to say this,
but you're ruining your own identity!
Without your antlers,
you're just a regular high school girl!
For the one who saved my life,
I'm willing to
put my character on the line!
Calm down!
It's too early to abandon your character!
It's still the first episode.
You don't want my crackers or my antlers.
They just stick back on?
Could it be?! What you're after is...
Me?!
Me = Venison
Why do you assume
I want deer-related things?!
Fine! Just eat me!
I'm not gonna eat you!
And who are those guys?
I don't have anything else to give you!
Look. As you can see,
I don't have any money.
You have more crackers?
Please. I have nothing left to give.
Why are you acting like
I'm extorting you?!
And for crackers?
Crap, I let my true self show.
Hey Nokotan,
are you and Koshi-san friends?
You sure look like it!
Huh? "Nokotan"?
That's my nickname! Cute, isn't it?
Wow, you're annoying.
You see, I was stuck on a utility pole
this morning, and Miss Delin—
Shikanoko-san!
I remembered the teacher called for you!
NO RUNNING IN THE HALLWAY
Oh, my. Koshitan, what are you thinking?
Bringing me to a place like this...
UNDER MAINTENANCE
STUDENT COUNCIL
How bold of you.
What are you imagining?!
Oh? That's what I should be asking you.
What? I-I'm not...
Koshitan...
Such a virgin.
Shut up!
And why are you calling me Koshitan?
It's your nickname.
We're Nokotan and Koshitan. Nice, right?
Are we some kind of comedy duo?
Who said you could give me a nickname?
Then we'll go with Miss Delinq—
Koshitan is fine.
It was fine after all.
That doesn't matter anyway.
Now, about my true identity.
Do you promise
you'll never tell anyone, ever?
I happen to be an honor
student at this school
and it'd be troublesome
if anyone found out.
If you say anything,
it won't end well for you.
Got it?
UNDER MAINTENANCE
STUDENT COUNCIL
Your true identity...
Does that mean that you're actually a virgin?
You're... not wrong, but no!
Damn it... Where do you
get off teasing me like that?
Listen up! Those antlers
better be your only joke!
You're right...
These antlers are kinda weird.
SHE'S INDOORS
Well... no...
A girl with antlers is totally gross.
What even is a deer, anyway?
I'm sorry if I made you uncomfortable.
I see...
She's lived through years
of people talking about her appearance.
And yet I...
Forget being an honor student.
I've failed at being a human!
I... I'm sorry!
I don't care about your antlers!
How about this?
Koshitan, frozen with fear,
was unable to ask where the horns started.
Today was exhausting.
I still have to study for tomorrow.
CREAK! CRASH!
What was that?
From over there?
Excuse me! Is anyone in there?
I just heard a loud noise and...
DEER
Do I call the police?! A doctor?!
Detective Conan? Er, no... Hajime-chan!
Hey, Koshitan!
Shikanoko-san, is that blood?
Did something happen?
Oops, my bad.
I fell from the ladder
and scraped my knee!
What about your head?!
What a cute bandage.
Shut up!
What are you doing in this
abandoned warehouse anyway?
I was cleaning.
Cleaning? All by yourself?
Yep! Thanks, Koshitan!
All right, back to work!
Fine. I'll help you.
What? You will?
Y-You're hurt.
Who knows what'll happen
if I leave you here?
Yay! Thanks!
She is, without a doubt, a tsundere.
Cleaning is such a chore,
but you seem to be having fun.
Because I'm with you, Koshitan!
Huh?! That's too much. We're just cleaning.
Even cleaning can be fun
when you do it with a friend.
It looks much cleaner already!
Ukai-sensei?
Sensei, notsu!
Hey there, notsu!
Did you help her, Koshi-san?
Thank you! It must've been hard.
Not at all! It was a piece of cake.
I'm so glad you'll be joining
the Deer Club too, Koshi-san!
Of course— What now?
Deer Club?
Just as I promised,
feel free to use this room as you like!
Hooray!
Wait! What in the world is the Deer Club?
And who said I'd be joining?
What? You didn't hear about it?
I founded a Deer Club!
What the hell kinda club is that?
I promised her that if she cleaned up
this place, she could use it as a club room.
- Right?
"Right," my butt!
More importantly, I can't be seen
in a crazy club like this!
I'm so relieved.
You're so responsible and caring, Koshi-san.
Like a reliable older sister!
You're so cheerful and kind,
so this is bound to be a fun club.
It'll be like home for us!
You're also very smart,
so you might win some kind of award!
We might even get to the nationals!
With you on board, I'm sure
the Deer Club will do incredible things!
Leave it to me!
Koshitan is a pushover.
Okay, Shikanoko-san,
please fill in the club approval form.
'Kay!
Club name, Deer Club.
Club president, Koshi Torako.
Activities, mainly taking care of deer.
Wait a minute!
Why am I the club president?
- You're the president, Koshitan.
- You're the president, Koshi-san.
How am I the odd one out here?
It's the Deer Club, right?
There's a literal deer girl right here.
Why not make her president?
I see what you mean.
But here it says that
the Deer Club mainly takes care of deer.
Huh? Yes, it does...
Club member
I'll be the Deer Club's
resident deer, you see.
The Deer Club's resident deer?
Deer
And the president cares for her!
That's you, Koshitan!
I'm not on board with that.
What kind of club takes care of deer?
Is this an agricultural school?
Here. Submitted!
Okay! And submission accepted!
That easily?!
President, I'm counting on you
to look after Shikanoko-san.
I'll be in your care.
Okay.
Having said,
"Leave it to me!" with a smile,
it was too late for Koshitan to back down.
DEER CLUB
SEEKING NEW CLUB MEMBERS
The Deer Club is born! Yay!
This is an incredible turn
of events for one single day.
I'll bring more deer crackers tomorrow!
Well, whatever.
I guess you can get started
by giving me a good brushing.
You've gotta be kidding!
And what's with the weird brush?
It's for animals.
Fine! Let's just get it over with.
Notsu!
Damn it. Why me?
Damn it... Am I going to
have to do this all the time?
Damn you, you vermin!
Y-Yikes!
I have no idea what's going on,
but it appears
the Deer Club's fight is just beginning!